prsguitars.com 2019-06-06

# PRS Guitars PRS Guitars Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting www.prsguitars.com. We are committed to protecting your privacy and we voluntarily provide this privacy statement in support of this commitment. PRS Guitars wants to provide a secure, helpful experience for our users. Therefore, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that the information you provide and submit to us remains private and is used only for the purposes as set forth herein.

The following discloses our current information gathering and dissemination practices, which may change from time to time.

## Personal Information Gathering

No user information is required to visit the PRS website. The only personal information gathered from you will be your e-mail address, should you choose to elect to provide your e-mail address. This address will be used to send you notices about PRS products and events.  _The information will NOT be revealed to third parties._

## Non-Personal Information Gathering

We will collect no personally identifiable information about you the user unless you choose to provide personal information to us. Therefore, if you do nothing but browse through the site or download information from the site, no personal information will be gathered. However, we will gather and store certain information that does not identify you personally. Such nonpersonal information may include the Internet domain name and the Internet Protocol address from which you access the site; the type of browser and operating system used to access the site; the date and time you access the site; the address of any website from which you used a link to access the site; and the site pages, areas and services you accessed during your visit. This nonpersonal information helps us determine what services and tools are most beneficial to our users and how we can best serve our users.

We have implemented Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising (Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting). You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings. In addition, you can use the [Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) to disable tracking by Google Analytics. We will use the data provided by Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to develop the site and content around our users’ interests and to help refine our advertising strategies.

PRS Guitars uses one or more companies to place advertisements for our products and services and those of third parties on our Site and third-party sites. Cookies and other technologies such as Web beacons or tags are used to measure the effectiveness of our ads and to determine the display of content and advertising to you based on your interests both on our site , as well as on third-party sites where you may visit. To support this interest based advertising solution, we, and companies who we have contracted with, may use anonymous information about your visits to our and other websites. The information collected and used by this process is always anonymous, and does not enable any third-party to identify you individually.

Although it is our hope that you find the display of advertising to you based on your anonymous interests valuable, if you would prefer not to participate in the services offered through these solutions, you can always opt-out of this activity by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website by clicking <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

## Specific Information Gathering

Contact information may be used to contact you when necessary. The information may also be used to inform you of additional services or of Site changes.

During your visit, PRS Guitars may ask you to choose to provide survey information. This information is requested in an effort to deliver to you the most relevant information and to provide you the best possible experience on this site.

Demographic and profile data is used to tailor each visitor's experience at our site; to provide content that we think each visitor might find of interest; to display content according to each visitor's preferences; and to create individualized database search criteria to accelerate each visitor's search process.

## Sharing of Information

PRS will not sell, rent, or otherwise transfer your information. PRS may however share broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information with our business partners. This aggregate information does not contain any personal information which can identify any individual user.

While PRS strives to protect the personal information of our users, PRS will release personal information if required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary.

## Acceptance of Terms

Your use of this site indicates an acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such usage.

## Changes To Privacy Policy — Modification and Termination of This Agreement

PRS reserves the right to update or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner which materially differs from the standards in effect at the time such information was collected, we will notify you, and you will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our site notifying users that our Privacy Policy has changed. In some cases when we post such a notice, we will also send an e-mail to users who have provided their information notifying them of the changes in our Privacy Policy.

## Contact Information

As noted, any contact information (such as email address) is used to contact the visitor when necessary.

## Third Party Websites and Links

The Site may contain links to other sites. Once you link to another site(s), you are subject to the privacy policy and terms of use of the new site(s). Paul Reed Smith Guitars is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Paul Reed Smith Guitars is not responsible to any third party posting to this Site. Please refer to our Terms of Use for other information pertinent to links to external sites.

## Children

The Site is not directed to children and it does not specifically collect information from children under the age of thirteen (13); therefore, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) does not apply to the Site. We highly recommend that parents view with their children the [Federal Trade Commission's Web site](https://www.ftc.gov/tips-advice/business-center/privacy-and-security/children%27s-privacy) to learn more about how COPPA protects children's privacy online.

## Contacting The Website

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, you can contact:

  * Paul Reed Smith Guitars
  * c/o Webmaster
  * PRS Guitars
  * 380 Log Canoe Circle
  * Stevensville, MD 21666
  * You can send an email to our webmaster [by clicking here](mailto:webmaster@prsguitars.com/)
